从一个活动中移动。在这种情况下，
To move from one activity. In this case,
我们的阳光应用程序里的主活动，另外，这边这个是细节活动，
the MainActivity in our sunshine app, to another, here
我们叫他开始活动。但是注意当我们
the DetailActivity, we call StartActivity. But note that when
使用开始活动这个方法时，并不是指出这个活动的类名称
using the StartActivity method, rather than specifying the class
就立即开始了，类名称
name of the activity to start directly, that
就直接被打包在了一个意图里。
class name is packaged explicitly within an intent. The
这个最基础的前提是很简单的。不管什么时候你需要让你的
basic premise is simple. Whenever you need your app
应用程序组件进行互相交流，或者是系统之间，
components to communicate with each other, or the system,
你就可以用意图来识别认定的终点。
you use intents to identify the
在你的开发程序下启动活动是
target destination. Starting activities within your
最简单的例子。
app is the simplest example. [SOUND]
通过使用环境和活动的一个类名称
With your intent explicitly indicating the target
与你的意图明确指示目标。意图使用
using the context and a class name of the activity. Intents that use the
你认准的组件的名字，就是为了然你知道这个是明确的意图。
name of the component you're targeting directly, are known as explicit intents.